Gustavo E. L'Eglise

Web Developer

Mexico City, Mexico (GMT-6) (+52) 5554134502 tavoleglise@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/gustavoleglise/ temp-portfolio-xi.vercel.app

Web developer with 5 years of experience. I'm really passionate about web development and currently Interested in the entire frontend spectrum, especially in React. Looking for a positive team to work and learn with.

EXPERIENCE

LALEO (Mexico City)

Javascript Developer — August, 2023 - Today

- Create, fix and update modules using ReactJs and NodeJs for an E-Commerce platform specialized in the sale of medical equipment and educational resources, visited by thousands of users daily.
- Designed, maintained, and improved modules using ReactJS and NodeJS for an innovative educational platform tailored to the needs of aspiring medical professionals.

Tech Stack: HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Redux, NodeJs, Express, SQL.

Freelancer (Mexico City)

Frontend Developer —February, 2023 - August, 2023

- Developed 3d web experiences using React and javascript 3D libraries like Three Js and Three Fiber.
- Modeled 3d environments optimized for web applications and browser deployment.

Tech Stack: Javascript, ReactJs, ThreeJs, Blender.

Parallax Ink (Mexico City)

Frontend Developer —march, 2018 - February, 2022

- Developed stunning and appealing web pages and web applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React from concept and design through development, deployment, and maintenance, working with creatives, designers, and project managers.
- Decrease errors percent from projects.
- Improved communication between the design and development teams thanks to my creative and technical background.
- Implemented modules that included 3D elements to improve the user experience and data visualization using javascript 3D libraries like Three Js and React Three Fiber.
- Created the company's main web page increasing engagement and user impressions on search engines.
- Created Web pages using WordPress CMS.
- Worked to achieve a balance between functionality and appeal in my projects.

Tech Stack: HTML, CSS, Javascript, WordPress, ReactJs.

Vector 3 (Mexico City)

Web Developer — October, 2017 - February, 2018

- Developed sections from a cryptocurrency exchange web application improving the data visualization and information reading on the page using Angular.
- Implemented Virtual reality experiences for web using Aframe JavaScript web library.

Tech Stack: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Angular, Typescript.

Unity Developer — October, 2016 - October, 2017

- Optimized 3D environments for performance optimization, decreasing applications loading time by 50%.
- Created UI elements for the AR and VR applications improving info visualization for the user.

Tech Stack: Unity, C#.

SKILLS

Programming Languages / Languages: Advanced: JavaScript, HTML, CSS; Intermediate: TypeScript; Basic: Python, PHP, C#. **Frameworks / Libraries:** ReactJs, ThreeJs, SASS, Tailwind, REST API, Bootstrap, WordPress, NodeJs, Express, Redux, NextJs, Jest, Astro, Angular, Vite, Vercel, Framer Motion, GSAP, NestJs

Database: SQL.

Tools: Github, Visual Studio Code, Jira.

Agile: Scrum.

Languages: Advanced: English; Native: Spanish.

Gustavo E. L'Eglise

Web Developer

Mexico City, Mexico (GMT-6) (+52) 5554134502 tavoleglise@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/gustavoleglise/ temp-portfolio-xi.vercel.app

EDUCATION

Instituto Tecnológico de Estudios Superiores de Monterrey – Mexico City, Bachelor of Art, *Digital Animation & Computer Graphics, minor in Computer science, May 2016.*

CERTIFICATIONS

ThreeJs Journey by Bruno Simon – 2021.

Platzi React and frontend set of courses – 2020.

Ihatetomatoes React & GSAP course – 2019.